Guide to the Gay Games collection, 1993-1994
Gay Games collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Gay Games collection, 1993-1994
7813
Gay Games collection
1.5 cubic ft.
Memorabilia, photographs, and newspapers.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Memorabilia from the 1994 Gay Games, including registration packets, photographs, ephemera, T-shirts, periodicals and newspapers.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Memorabilia from the 1994 Gay Games, including registration packets, photographs, ephemera, T-shirts, periodicals and newspapers. This Collection also includes some memorabilia from the 25th anniversary of the Stonewall riots since both events took place in New York City in June, 1994.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Gay Games collection
Subjects:
Gay men -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State).; Lesbians -- Societies and clubs -- New York (State).
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Gay Alliance of the Genesee Valley records
NOTES
Arrangement and description of the Gay Games collection, #7813 made possible in part by a grant from the Documentary Heritage Program of the New York State Archives, a program of the State Education Department
CONTAINER LIST
- 3 registration packets, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Gay Games - Maps, programs and ephemera, June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Includes tickets, programs, a commemorative plastic bag and pen, NYC subway and bus maps.
- Photographs, June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  14 envelopes
- "Out", June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Out", July-August 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The Holly Cole Trio, 1994; TR-10511 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Free cassette tape with "out" magazine
- 10 Percent - "Stonewall", June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- MetroSource, Summer 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- The List Magazine, June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- POZ, June-July 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Gay Games and Cultural Festival IV - Official Program, June 18-25, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- New York Pride Guide, June 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Greenwich Village Press, June 1994 (Box 2)
- Stonewall News, June 20, 1994 (Box 2)
- Stonewall News, June 27, 1994 (Box 2)
- The Village Voice, June 21, 1994 (Box 2)
- The Village Voice, June 28, 1994 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV hat with Rochester Pride pin, 1994; MU-2185 (Box 2)
- Gay Games medal, June 1994; MU-2186 (Box 2)
- Bag of pins for Gay Games and other gay related events, c. 1994; MU-2187 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV key chain, 1994; MU-2188 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV plastic flag, 1994; MU-2189 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV T-shirt (black), 1994; MU-2190 (Box 2)
- Team Dallas T-shirt, undated; MU-2191 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV T-shirt (yellow), 1994; MU-2192 (Box 2)
- Team Northampton T-shirt, 1994; MU-2193 (Box 2)
- Marcella Detroit "I Believe", 1994; CD-2209 (Box 2)
- The Gay Games '94 Commemorative CD, 1994; CD-2210 (Box 2)
- Gay Games IV Figure Skating, June 24, 1994; V-7208 (Box 2)
- March on Washington T-shirt, 1993; MU-2194 (Box 2)
- Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network - Equality March in Washington D.C. T-shirt, October 2009; MU-2195 (Box 2)
- Aids Walk Genesee Valley T-shirt, 2010; MU-2196 (Box 2)
  Gift of Sean Soper
- Rochester Victory Alliance T-shirt, undated; MU-2197 (Box 2)
- GAGV Rochester Pride T-shirt, 2010; MU-2198 (Box 2)
- GALAXE T-shirt, undated; MU-2199 (Box 2)
- Stonewall 25 T-shirt, 1994; MU-2200 (Box 2)
- Stonewall 25 pin, June 1994; MU-2201 (Box 2)